So, hi everyone. Welcome back to Data
Science in a Pocket, and we have a great
news for you that is Kimiko 2.6 free API
is live now. Yes, you heard it right. It
is one of the best open source AI models
that is available. Though the size of
the model is huge and hence you can't
run it locally in your system. But but
but I think Nvidia being so generous,
they have again given us the free access
to Kimiko 2.6 with 40 RPM, that is 40
requests per minute for one of the best
AI models in open source arena competing
with as you can see on the screen
looking at the benchmarks even with the
frontier models too that are closed
source. So, in this short video I'll be
explaining you the codes
and what code to use and how to generate
the free API key for using Kimiko 2.6,
the best open source model so far. Here
you can see the benchmarks for general
agents, coding, everywhere Kimiko 2.6 is
looking quite competitive with other AI
models. It's long horizon coding. There
are multiple different information about
the model that we've already covered in
the previous videos that you can check
out. But for now, this video is not
focusing on the details of Kimiko 2.6.
But but but we are looking into how to
access the model for free without using
GPUs with free API.
Coding driven design as you can see. So,
I've opened up Nvidia Names page. I'll
be sharing the URL for the page here
only and I have selected at the top left
you can see
Moonshot AI Kimiko 2.6. You can even
chat with the model for free. Try out
any query. As you can see I'm using what
is number larger 9.11 or 9.
8. As you can see on the top right, you
can generate the codes for free and
there's a Python code. Just copy paste
it. Click on the generate API key. For
that, first of all, log in into your
Nvidia account. You need to create an
Nvidia account for this so that you can
generate the free API key for yourself.
Now, once you click on generate API key,
at the bottom you can see the API has
been created. Don't try to copy my API
keys because I won't be sharing this. It
will get deleted. So, try to create your
own. Here I have copy pasted the code in
Google Colab as you can see as it is.
Just change the prompt if you wish to in
the content section as you can see here
and hit enter.
Here you can see that the output here
here has come in in JSON format and
output looks quite interesting. It's
quite lengthy. I'm not jumping on the
details of the model how and the quality
of the output, but just to show you how
to use the free API key. Try out another
prompt. Hey, buddy, what's up?
Just checking the API key. How much can
you use it? You can use 40 RPM, that is
40 requests per minute. It's not It's
kind of unlimited, but it's quite good
for experimental projects that you're
building. So, it is giving output for
this also. So, now you can use one of
the most
capable AI models in the open source
arena Kimiko 2.6 for free using the free
API key. And not just that, you can use
many other models that are present in
Nvidia Names. You can check out from the
top left catalog where you can see other
models too.
And you can run this code anywhere,
Google Colab, Google Colab, your local
host because it doesn't require any GPU
also.
So, with this we'll try to wrap this up.
Do try out the codes. The link is in the
comment section below for you to use it.
Thank you so much. I hope you have a
great day.